wallpaper777.com 2015-03-17

# Privacy Policy - desk7.net

Wellcome to desk7.net, In this website we have collected all kinds of desktop wallpapers, All wallpapers are free for you to download, Wish you find the beautiful wallpapers for your desktop !  
Every wallpapers has 9 size:1024x768 1280x1024 1600x1200 1920x1440 1280x800 1440x900 1680x1050 1920x1200 2560x1600,Don't forget to bookmark us, the site is updated daily. 

**_[desk7.net](http://desk7.net/)_** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site.

**Advertisers**

Third Party Advertising  
We use other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

Third Party Cookies  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

**Personal Information**

This Web site does allow user to enter their email address at their own will for subscription in our newsletter. We do not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted.

Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes.

** Use of Cookies: 
** desk7.net employ cookies in order to allow us to know if user have the site software "Cool Wallpaper Software" installed so that users can download photo from us. We do not use cookies to track user activities in anyway. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser. 

** desk7.net Membership Site & Software Terms: 
** All members that purchased the "desk7.net Membership Software" made have access to the full version of the "Cool Wallpaper Software". This purchase gives license for one single user only and full version of desk7.net Software may only be installed in one single computer only. 
  
All individuals ordering online are required to provide their Name, Address, Email address and credit card information via a secure SSL (Secure Socket Layer) webpage on an Authorize.net secure server. Authorize.net is our online payment gateway provider and is the World's leading online payment authorization service. SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption technology scrambles all the information being transmitted, making it virtually impossible for it to be stolen or intercepted. SSL is the Internet standard for conducting business online. 
  
Membership Information of all orders are stored in our database to keep as record and is used to provide members access to area within desk7.net that requires a password and login. It is also used to verify the identity of member's who have misplaced their passwords. In the event that a user's email address is not valid written communication will be sent to their physical address as listed in our database. All personal information is held in the strictest of confidence and will NOT be given to any third party. 
  
User may cancel their purchase of the "Cool Wallpaper Software" if it does not work correctly on their computer by emailing support@desk7.net and providing their email and password information within 30 days. 
  
**External Links**

This site contains links to other sites. **_[desk7.net](http://desk7.net/)_** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us: [CLICK HERE](http://desk7.net/contactusform.shtml)

©2010 desk7.net All Rights Reserved. [HOME](http://www.desk7.net/) | Help/Support Page | Terms of Use | Link To Us | Link Exchange | Sitemap | Wallpapers Searches | Privacy Policy | Contact Us Apple wallpapers, Cars wallpapers, Christmas wallpapers, Hot wallpapers, Sexy wallpapers, Girls wallpapers, Babes wallpapers,  
Halloween wallpapers, Microsoft wallpapers, Wallpaper, Free wallpapers, Desktop wallpapers, Desktop backgrounds, Free desktop wallpapers, Free stock photos
